The story of the greatest rivalry in motorsport.
Race for Glory: Audi vs. Lancia is a drama, history
film directed by Stefano Mordini.
Inspired by true events that occurred during the fierce rivalry between Germany
(Audi) and Italy (Lancia) at the 1983 Rally World Championships.
Cesare Fiorio, played by Riccardo Scamarcio.
Walter Röhrl, played by Volker Bruch.
Roland Gumpert, played by Daniel Brühl.
Jane McCoy, played by Katie Clarkson-Hill.
Michèle Mouton, played by Esther Garrel.
Ennio, played by Giorgio Montanini.
Race for Glory: Audi vs.
Lancia is a 2024 motor racing film co-produced between Italy and Britain, directed by Stefano Mordini from the script written by Filippo Bologna, Mordini, and Riccardo Scamarcio, produced by
Scarmarcio and Jeremy Thomas for Recorded Picture Company, as well as Lebowski, HanWay Films and Metropolitan Films; and with Daniel Brühl and Scamarcio in starring roles.
Based on true events, the film depicts the rivalry between Roland Gumpert's team driving the Audi Quattro and
the team of Cesare Fiorio in the Lancia 037 rally car at the 1983 World Rally Championship.
The film was simultaneously released in cinemas and
on video on demand on 5 January 2024.
The film explores themes of car race, italy, europe, based on true story, audi.
The tone is emotional.